Cracking shot excellent four straight away
HM Sports ticket counter
hello and welcome back once again
ICC Lombard Brokers Premier League
2025 second
semi-final MIBL vs Howdun
so MBL one toss elected to field first after one over
see
loss excellent shot last
ball of the previous over four runs it a
very good catch looking to play for the
big one just
shot an excellent catch taken he was long
on catch taken by
Harshad Vishal Jadhav this
time unlucky 1.26 Howdun
not a new badder Rama
Krishnan first ball looking to play on side
got edge and good call from Mitesh Patil to
quick single taken
1.3 a semi-final two in
progress excellent bowling good
bowling turned the match of seven eight overs into a test match
Praful Navale
1.47 f
Howdun all around MBL's Brown Munde
Howdun's batsmen Ramakrishna and Mitesh
Patil
1.58 a Howdun
very good bowling from Praful just  2.49 Done outside off,
1 wicket taken by KL Rahul Howden 11 off 1 ...
Sandeep Sal ​​hits the last ball for just five runs
and sends it to the backward region. The
fielder tries to hit
it but the ball goes away. Four runs. Nice
scoop
shot [Music] and done.
3rd one for 18. Two overs. One ball. 18 runs and
wicket. Howden
score. Very well played short pitch ball.
Tried to hit a big shot but with slow pace it
confused the batsman. Good start here. MIBL
bowling
unit manages to take two wickets.
3.2 19 is two.
So we are
back. Ramakrishnan lets play towards
Langan. F
single.
3.5 21. Howden semi-final two in progress. A
game is lightly cut
and steals a run.
Four overs over. 21. Fatu
[Music]
Howden. So 21 and psv 22 so f 22 for two.
Elegantly played towards point by
Ramakrishna and single. Run
taken. Excellent start here. MIBL
team.
Very well played umpire
checking.  KRNER region to get six runs very well
played
Aniket Kerkar has hit
4.5 now setting up the big target how
done different type of
shot scoop shot at the back region
five overs game over 33 how
done 33 five overs 33 for two taken very
good catch catches the third
wicket fall how done
MI BL all the Brown Munde Army are
doing a fantastic job yes no yes no
one run
shot so only single run will
count takes into the black
hole good bowling Sandeep Patel
5 off 35 three
howden and took very good catch Praful 11
number jersey remember the
name very good catch at long of the
region so one more wicket fall MI BL is
striking
well so Sandeep Patil strikes four balls
bowled two runs and two wickets in this
over and Ramakrishnan departs
seven runs 11 balls completely pressure is on here
semi final now this will be to be seen
Who comes with the dazzler? The
second
finalist 5 D Cha 35 P
Char Nimit Ra is now the new batsman
Six overs over Four for 38
Howdone good fielding
performance Howdone has completely done it all
MIBL fielders good
team good support good
crowd ICC Lomber Brokers Premier
League
2025 semi-final two in progress something
special upper
cut plays two backward region only single
run 6 D Cha Char Howdone
alti turn
shot this is going to go
behind GI lead feeder running to catch General Insurance
lead and good fielding
late 6 P2 42
6 Dti 424
Howdone Mani Trivedi A Nimit
Ra lets see how much will we do something to the
board good bowling unit Aaron Sree 1.3
runs proof Navale Swe Sandhi Ptu
total impact on
Howdone completely made this match
box cricket here MIBL
fielders
6.5
4344 No one is giving any chance to hit big shots here. Will go for
two runs. Run
fast for two
runs. The over will end with two runs. Seven
overs of the game are over. 45 fo Coming up final over
of the first innings
7.16 fo Coming up last fo Balls of the
first innings Semi-final to
already one final entered an dazzler first
finalist
so dot ball four balls
left 464 7 the two
Howden very good bowling
well bowled MI BL have mastered
in bowling
logistics inside edge
not giving any chance to score runs here. Quality
bowling performance from MI BL
First ball one run and three dots Last two
balls this time wide ball outside the line S Mim
Singh 47 74 done
and is out Finally did not get a wicket on non-strike end got
on strike
Looking for the run and
gun 49 score
no
two sa 4 fi Coming up last ball of
first
innings IC Lord Brokers Premier
League Day two
season
two semi-final
to so here we go Coming up last ball first
Innings Sandeep
Patil into the block hole Very very good
bowling performance Umpire's out
sling So at overs got 49 for 5 and the
target to chase is 50 runs MI BL have to
win this match and
enter the finals We will take a short break Will be
back as
soon as possible
In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaa Lumberjack Health Insurance
[Music]
Jump Food Rang
Choice Energy
Low In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaa Lumberjack Health Insurance
Power Resto
[Music]
In the game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lumberjack Health Insurance
Jun Food
Raise Energy
Low In the game of life Stay protected with Aaaa
Lumberjack Health Insurance Pad
[Music]
So in the count of three to one here we go Let's
play make some noise once again Talia ho jaye
50 ka hai target Eight
overs Two runs in the first ball In the
feed Chase down towards
Pup couple of runs
Taken Vishal Jadhav Bowling Arshad Ansari
Akash  Lanjekar has
played defensively this time on the non-strike end, good
bowling by Vishal Yadav,
target given by me, how done to me, bill just
a single at short third
man, three, just bowled three, no loss, IBL
black hole, good bowling from Vishal
Yadav, signaling leg by
one over, game over, seven
runs needed in the innings, 43 runs,
ACB Premier League
2025 semi-final two in progress,
one team has entered the final, N Dazzlers,
now whoever wins this match will
play the final with N Dazzlers. Now
Aniket
Kerkar, Arshad Ansari,
strike, power, place on, one more over, just close, very close, stump, outside, leg by, white,
spare, Mr Prashant
Ray, after a, after one, no loss,
IBL 42, get from, sent, very
good cut shot, excellent cut
shot,
played in the gap for four runs, sent out of the crease,
umpire
enjoyed, just dancing away the signaling,
no loss  MBL
to was something different One hand
goes on the back foot Excellent placement and
steals a run
1.3 14 runs No wicket 36 runs The
fireworks have already begun Let's
turn for a six 1.3 14 f No
loss A typical tap shot played in Box
Cricket Single not
taken 1.41 f No loss The ball goes
into the backward zone Slowly slowly
it goes for
four One D Pa 19 no wicket
Target of 31 31 runs to be scored now 37 balls Target
is 50
runs required
This time directionless bowling White Sil Ba
Umpire 1.52 f No loss ME
BL cuts lightly towards point
and steals a run Over ends
After two o'clock 21 f No loss ME IBL 29 to get
36 balls
No 21 for no loss
D B C Umpire has declared the ball dead The ball should be revived
Good
bowling Advantage of being hidden Bowler
Ramakrishnan relieves the batsman
Length and troubling the batsman,
two off one 21 for no loss, will be looking for a wicket
now. Howden's
guns just
two off two runs, 27 runs needed now in the coming 5 overs,
easy
special
fielder at short cover, catching position, stop
single,
two off one, no wicket on 2, 57, 27
needed, 33
ball, a catch, dropped, dream
shattered, batsman wanted to play on the on side, got
top edge, looking London, talking, Tokyo, he got
top edge
2.5, 25
more runs needed, 25
runs half the job is done, half is left, the rest is left, he has
pulled it brilliantly
and made the ball
round, after CM's bar these four
umpires are
dancing, signalling for
four after three overs, 29 on 29, no wicket
now, 21 runs needed
MIBL will win this match easily in the coming five overs, very
good fielding at long on, only single run
conceded,
Vishal
Yadav on the field,
no wicket on 30, one, 30 runs, no wicket now  No, he has
played it towards mid-wicket for one
run now can they be in any
hurry MI BL have 19 runs and
balls left
28 bounces and 1 run gun for one bounce
into the fence Arshad Ansari has done a
great job Dull 1 for 8
gun catch taken by Rama Krishnan
last ball for the next
wicket so very well played Arshad Ansari 15
off 11 balls
15 needed now 26 balls for the first wicket
MI
BL time to perform now it's time to
join with the finalist NM Dazzlers who will
win and now it's chance for MI BL to
join with NM
Dazzlers 15 to get from
26 35 3.4
new batsman has come
Praful with two runs in the first ball
.  P 37 on
1 no from 25
single to end of the over four overs play is over
38 for one only 12 runs needed
in the next four overs
Ramakrishnan into the attack
white
ball
celebration advance fireworks are going on
on the sky
my way or else skyway
with good timing he has pulled it
and put the ball in the wrong direction towards the final
four so just seven runs to get for victory
MIBL they will enter into the final with
N
Dazzles now on a blank paper we will write N
Dazzles vs MIBL it will be the final
point region he has cut
4 P 2
44 S ry one big t and t t
well cut deep backward
point only a
single now they just
need five runs needed to win this match
and enter the final
Vijal MIBL
team very good cut
shot no ball no
ball at all it's end
of the match
MI BILL enter into the
final now come final
match MI
BILL so  The final match will start at
7:30 and before the toss